t-tapp.com 2009-06-22

# Help Desk - T-Tapp.com

| 

**home  
cellulite control  
the workout  
articles & exercises  
success stories  
newsletter  
mommy fitness  
t-tapp team  
help desk  
** |  | 

Privacy Policy

T-Tapp, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our **firm commitment to your privacy.** The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: T-Tapp.com 

We do not share any information about our users or customers with any third party.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. This gives T-Tapp an idea of which parts of our site users are visiting. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a users session will be tracked, but the user will be anonymous. 

We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Cookies, by themselves, cannot be used to find out the identity of any user. T-Tapp will only store information provided voluntarily, but this information is not personally identifiable. For your security and privacy, no payment, credit card, billing address, or any other personally identifiable information is stored in a cookie on your computer. 

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Other data collected from surveys is used for demographic purposes, to enhance our services for our visitors. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Contact information from the order form is used to send information about our company to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Information collected by T-Tapp.com will not be sold or redistributed in any manner and are held in the strictest confidence. 

T-Tapp uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience's demographics. This is essential to keeping our service free. We do not share information about individual users with any third party. 

Security: This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. A Secure Server Digital Certificate has been obtained from a valid Certificate Authority (CA) for www.T-Tapp.com from Thawte. This enables T-Tapp to use encryption technology to secure your data transmission and storage. 

We utilize industry standard SSL encryption when accepting your credit card or financial information on an application. In addition, we utilize the same encryption standard when transferring your data to our internal fulfillment system. 

Choice/Opt-Out: Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. You can manage your subscriptions, subscribe and unsubscribe from any and all newsletters at the following link: http://www.t-tapp.com/subscriptions

Correct/Update: Users may change or modify information previously provided using the functions on the site to update information. 

Contacting the Web Site: If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: 

Webmaster

T-Tapp, Inc.

1450 10th Street S.

Safety Harbor, FL 34695

<<< Back to Help Desk
